♪ Men. ♪
We got to go.
We just got here.
Yeah, I know, but I got to go.
The sit-down "go."
No, I am... I am tired
of being a slave
to your fear
of public bathrooms.
Do you know what people do
in there?
They go to the bathroom.
Exactly. It's-It's not the seat
as much as...
(whispers):
the splash.
You have ruined a lot of things
that I enjoy,
and I am not gonna let you
take pooping from me.
Oh, fine, but every time
you use a public bathroom,
you are putting your ass
against every other ass
that has ever been there.
See this guy?
I might as well rub
my naked butt all over his.
And he took pooping from me.
Excuse me. Walden?
Yes?
I-I'm sure
you don't remember me,
but I used to work for you.
Sorry, I don't
remember your name.
It's Nicole, but you'd always
call me Michelle.
Right! Michelle!
Yeah.
Hey.
How you doing?
I-I haven't seen you
around the office in a while.
Yeah, I stopped going in
after you fired me.
Oh. Wow.
That is...
Are you here to kill me?
I'm actually trying to get
a tech start-up off the ground.
Or as my mom calls it,
wasting 20 hours a day
in the garage
and not giving her grandkids.
Let me guess:
You're looking for help.
With the company,
not the grandkids.
I mean, not that
I wouldn't want to...
with you...
Can you talk now?
I am looking for help...
with the company.
I'll let you know
about the grandkids.
Well, I would love
to hear about it.
Why don't you call my office,
and we'll set something up?
Yeah, when I worked for you,
I was kind of in charge
So you get it.
(laughs)
Look, 15 years ago,
you cornered Bill Gates
in a steam room,
and you pitched him the idea
for Blungogo.com,
and six months later,
you were a billionaire.
Yeah, what you don't know is
that I also got Tased
in the nuts
by a security guard named Randy.
Look, I think
I have a really good idea.
Everything you need
to know is right in here.
Okay. I'll take a look at it.
Thank you.
I didn't even have to get
Tased in the lady nuts.
I still might Tase you later.
(laughs)
Oh, it's not weird.
We-we know each other.
I fired her.
I couldn't do it.
We got to go. Now. Now!
What?
This is not a drill!
Code brown!
I wonder if I could train him
to go in the yard.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ah.
♪ Men.
♪ Two and a Half Men 11x11 ♪
Tazed in the Lady Nuts
Original Air Date on January 2, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Men. ♪
(panting)
Wow.
Oh.
Yeah, that was fun.
(sighs)
Two thumbs up.
Felt like more than that.
Hey, uh, thanks
for letting me stay over.
Thanks for letting
me stay under.
Mmm.
You know, I've been thinking--
we've been doing this
for a couple of weeks,
and I don't know
that much about you.
Well, you know all
the important things.
My favorite color's pink,
my favorite singer is Pink,
my favorite
body part is...
Okay, fine.
If you don't want to talk,
we don't have to talk.
No, I'm kidding.
Come on, ask me anything.
Tell me about your family.
What's your mom like?
Well, she's very,
very pretty.
Mm-hmm.
Not too bright.
Her boyfriend went
to Harvard Law School,
and then broke up with her,
because he wanted a Jackie,
and she was more
of a Marilyn,
so she decided to
study real hard...
Hold on a second.
That's the plot
to Legally Blonde.
You saw that, huh?
Uh, all right, I'll-I'll...
I'll tell you the truth.
My mom is a
beautiful prostitute.
Oh.
And my dad,
Richard Gere...
You're unbelievable.
Cut me some slack!
I grew up in a town
that didn't allow dancing!
♪ Men. ♪
Mm. Good morning.
Actually, it's a great morning.
Somebody gave me
a billion-dollar idea.
Oh, you got my e-mail.
You know, with my idea.
The app that helps you find
a clean public restroom
anywhere in the world.
I called it "Crapster."
Yeah, as good of an idea
as that is,
and actually, it's not that bad,
I'm talking
about thought-recognition.
Thought-control computing.
Imagine you want to send a text,
but, uh, you don't want
to take your phone out.
Or, imagine you want
to change the channel on the TV,
but you don't have a remote.
Imagine
you're in a strange city,
and you can't find
a clean bathroom.
Imagine you're in Italy,
and you have to "arriva-doody."
You know what?
Here is a hundred dollars.
I just bought your idea.
Now, stop talking about it.
Deal. Looks like I am getting
that filling after all.
Morning.
Good morning.
Oh, hey, morning.
What are you guys up to today?
I don't know.
Maybe we'll go to a bar
and let guys buy us drinks
if we're willing
to make out with each other.
ALLAN:
Wait.
Is-is that a thing?
You and I should run that scam
with girls.
Hey, I've got an idea.
Let's go for a hike
in the canyon.
I'd rather stay home
and yodel in your canyon.
♪ Yodel-ay-hee hoo-ha!
Come on, let's get
some fresh air, hang out.
Just the two of us.
Uh, yeah. Yeah, why not?
Sounds great.
(clears her throat)
Do you guys want to join us?
Sure.
You can never have
too much wood in the forest.
I can't. I'm busy.
Always busy.
I can't remember the last time
this one took me anywhere.
Hey, uh, Jenny,
here's a hundred dollars.
Lose him in the forest.
♪ Men. ♪
Yes?
Yeah, I'm looking for Nicole.
Are you my new dad?
Excuse me?
It's a joke.
Try to keep up.
Who are you?
I'm Walden Schmidt.
Holy Schmidt!
Oh, my God.
Mr. Schmidt,
it is such an honor to meet you.
I have a poster of you.
A poster?
Yeah, yeah, check it out.
I made it in college.
WALDEN:
Wow. It's, uh...
Wow.
I cut and pasted Laura Dern's
hair onto your face.
It's pretty breathtaking, right?
I'm sorry... uh, who are you?
Oh, uh, I-I'm Barry.
Barry Foster.
But you can call me "BF,"
as in your biggest fan.
(laughs)
Walden!
Nicole, hi.
I read your proposal.
I'm interested.
Really?
This is amazing.
(laughing)
Oh, my fan fiction's come true.
NICOLE:
Barry,
we talked about this.
Right, right.
Boundaries.
All right, here's-here's
what I'm prepared to do.
In return for 51%
of your company,
and him never
hugging me again,
I will back
your project.
I don't think I can do that.
Neither do I.
(laughs)
Barry!
Okay.
Look, I can't give up control.
This company is my baby.
But I will sell you
a minority share
if you agree to work
as my product engineer.
Oh, product engineer?
I mean, do I look like Barry?
No offense, Barry.
Did you hear that?
He knows my name.
I'm sorry, that's all
I can offer you.
Well, then it's a pass.
All right, thanks
for stopping by.
No, no, no, come on, this
isn't how the story ends.
Hold on. Th...
That's it?
No negotiating?
You heard my offer.
There's also a
supplemental offer--
uh, best friends for life.
All right, wait.
All right, fine. I...
I will... work for you,
but I still need
a majority position.
Good-bye, Mr. Schmidt.
What are you, like, some
kind of evil Bond villain?
All right... all right,
all right, fine!
Deal.
I'll... be your number two.
(clearing throat)
Well...
it'd actually be
number three, but...
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, thank God.
(panting)
I'm coming, Charlie.
I hope you have a guest room
in heaven.
You shouldn't
feel so bad.
He's in pretty good shape
for a guy in his 60's.
He's 45.
Whoa.
I'll be right back.
Ah... uh... do you mind?
Actually...
(screams)
Aah! It burns!
It burns!
That's because it's vodka.
Who brings vodka on a hike?
Someone who thinks
hikes should be fun.
Okay, that's it,
I'm packing it in.
I think I saw a mom with a
stroller.
I'm gonna hitch a ride
back downhill.
No, no, no, no, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Don't leave me alone
with Brooke.
What? Why not?
She's great.
Well, here's the thing.
She's-she's...
she's always trying to...
get to know me.
That bitch.
She's always asking me
these-these personal things.
You know?
"What are your dreams?"
"What was your childhood like?"
"What's your last name?"
You are just like your dad.
He'd never open up to anybody
'cause he was afraid
of rejection,
so he'd reject them first.
I don't want to
reject Brooke.
So, let her in.
If you don't take a chance,
you haven't got one.
Do you think I really believed
that a complete stranger
would let me live
in his Malibu beach house
forever?
No. But I took a chance,
and it paid off.
♪ Men. ♪
(speaking lyrics): Everybody get up,
everybody get up...
(singing):
♪ Hey, hey, hey
♪ Hey, hey, hey...
Hey, hey, hey!
Oh, sorry.
Sometimes
when I'm writing code,
I get kind of lost
in my dope jams.
Well, if you're gonna play
music, just play it out loud.
You got it, number three.
♪ Talk about getting blasted
(singing along):
♪ I hate these blurred lines
♪ I know you want it
(singing along):
♪ I know you want it,
but you're ♪
♪ A good girl
♪ The way you grab me
♪ Talkin' 'bout gettin' nasty ♪
♪ Go ahead, get at me
♪ Everybody get up
♪ What do they make dreams for
♪ When you got them jeans on
♪ What do we need steam for
♪ You the hottest bitch
♪ In this place
Hey, hey, hey!
♪ You want to hug me...
(music stops)
It was the new guy's idea.
I was...
What's that, Barry?
I can't hear you
from all the way under this bus.
So, how's the code coming?
Actually, you know,
I had a thought.
Um, if we reconfigure
this kernel,
we're gonna save
a lot of time and money.
Yeah, it's-it's good.
(high-pitched): It's just,
uh... eh, it's-it's good.
Wha-What do you think,
Barry?
(high-pitched):
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's-it's good. It's good.
Why do you guys keep talking
with high voices?
Why do you keep saying,
(high-pitched): "It's good"?
It is good.
Just, you know, for...
mmm... 2002.
Ouch.
I believe the correct
terminology in 2002
was, "Oh, snap."
(clears throat)
Okay. Um...
you know, I've been... I've
been doing this for a...
a really long time,
and I've-I've been
really successful.
I know. We studied you
in school.
Oh, I get it. You guys... you
guys are saying that I'm old?
No.
Yeah.
I thought we were going
a different way.
Look, I respect you
enormously, but...
I got to go with my gut.
Okay. No problem.
You're the boss.
Thank you.
Now, who wants Chinese?
Are you paying?
'Cause I forgot my wallet...
Yes, Barry.
Hey, I got one
just like him at home.
Boy, oh, boy, you could cut
the sexual tension back there
with a knife.
Think she's into me?
No, not you. Me.
Me and her have had this whole
"will they, won't they" thing
going on for some time now.
So it's like a...
Ross/Rachel thing?
Who?
Are those friends of yours?
Oh, God. I am old.
But with age comes wisdom.
(clears throat)
We're gonna do this my way.
What?
Nicole is wrong about the code.
I'm sending you a file.
We're gonna rewrite it.
Oh, this is bad.
This is bad.
I'm stuck between my hero
and-and the future mother
of my children.
Come on, Barry.
Don't you want to be
on a poster with me?
Hop on the eagle, man.
Let's soar together.
I don't know. I don't...
I don't know.
You know you want it.
♪ You know you want it
♪ You know
you want it ♪
♪ I'm a good girl
♪ Men. ♪
Oh, good. You're home.
I need to talk to you.
Oh,
you know, actually, I'm not.
I'm just here
for the essentials.
Shower, change of clothes, bag
of performance-enhancing weed.
Th-This won't take long.
Uh, will you look
at this picture?
Let me see.
Was this taken
from the Mars rover?
No, that's my balls.
(groans)
Dude! What the hell?
They've been burning
ever since I went on that hike.
Maybe somebody's talking
about 'em.
No, I'm serious.
What could it be?
I don't know.
What, like, poison oak?
I did take a leak in the bushes.
And yet you couldn't go
in a coffee shop.
Just look at the picture.
Yeah. Fine.
I can't believe I'm gonna...
zoom in on your balls.
I'm not gonna be able to...
Oh, my God.
It's a tick.
What?
You got a tick on your junk.
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, God!
What's with him?
He's got a tick on his 'nads.
Huh. I never thought anything
could live off Zippy.
♪ Men. ♪
I don't see how this is gonna
make us more productive,
but I really don't care.
And that is the beauty of pot.
(chuckles)
You got work to do,
you don't care.
You got bills to pay,
you don't care. (chuckles)
You see a picture
of your roommate's gonads...
you care.
(chuckles)
But the image is fading.
Yeah, marijuana is excellent.
I don't know why I waited
this long to try it.
Wait a second--
you've never been high before?
I wanted it to be special.
And now I can tell everybody
my first time
was with Walden Schmidt.
Hey, when you tell that story,
maybe throw in
a few more details.
(chuckles) Hey, aren't you glad
we took a second to relax?
Mmm. Totally.
You know, I kind of forgot
the meaning of the word "relax""
Relax, relax, relax.
Oh, God. I don't remember
what it means either.
I'm losing my words.
No, this is exactly, exactly
what the commercials
warned me about.
Barry, calm down.
Just take a deep breath,
close your eyes, count to ten.
All right, I trust you
with my life.
You're my best friend.
One...
two...
Oh, my God, we have ice cream
sandwiches in the freezer.
Hey, man, grab me one!
Mmm, no,
grab me two!
I want to make
an ice cream sandwich sandwich.
That is an awesome idea.
Are you staring at me
or am I just really paranoid?
There's nothing
to be paranoid about.
She's on to us. Abort.
I repeat, abort.
I hate you.
You don't.
You like me.
You know what. Doesn't matter.
Because I have a policy
about dating people I work with.
Yeah, but it's
your policy, so...
you can break it.
You're the boss.
I am, aren't I?
I guess that makes me
the wo-man.
You guys.
I got great news.
Ice cream sandwiches are
in the oven.
They'll be ready in five.
♪ Men. ♪
You want a refill?
Uh, no, I-I don't want
to get drunk.
Oh, my God, did I somehow
get you pregnant?
I want to get
to know you better,
and I don't want anything
to get in the way of that.
I really like you. Um...
That's new for me.
Hey, I feel the exact same way.
I've never felt this vulnerable
with someone.
You know, when it didn't involve
a safe word.
So what are we gonna do?
We can start by being honest
with each other.
That's horrible.
Hey.
Come on. Let's do this.
Tell me a secret, something
you've never told anyone else.
Something is wrong
with my balls.
Something like that.
I just... I-I had a tick
and I pulled it off
and now they won't stop swelling
and I'm afraid
they're gonna explode.
So why are you telling us?
Because Brooke works in a salon.
She waxes people. Maybe she's
seen something like this before.
All right, l-let's see.
Oh!
Oh...
Boy, if I wasn't gay before...
♪ Men. ♪
(exhales)
Check it out, dude.
Where's your other hand
in that picture?
What the hell?
Three people can't fit
on an eagle.
You-you changed my code.
Yeah. I made it better.
No, you didn't.
We went over this.
(chuckles) Okay. Everybody who's
made a billion dollars
off their software in this room,
raise your hand.
(gasps, chuckles)
Look at that. It's just me.
Okay.
Everyone who owns 51% of
this company, raise their hand.
(chuckles)
Look at that. Just me.
Everybody who's still
a little high
and is worried that that's...
never gonna stop,
raise your hand.
Crap. That's just me.
Listen, just go
with me on this.
No, I don't work
for you anymore.
Okay, look, I know you think
you know what you're doing.
But, trust me, you don't.
And I know you think
you still work here,
but, trust me, you don't.
You're fired.
(whirring)
Oh, snap.
Look, I-I was just trying
to help.
Well, it's gonna take me a day
to undo your "help."
A day? Come on.
I can undo this in an hour.
You should just...
you should just go, dude.
Okay.
Fine.
If that's what you want.
It is.
Barry, it was an honor
to fly with you.
Honor was all mine.
At ease.
All right.
Oh, uh, one last thing.
We're done.
I don't work with you anymore.
That's what
"you're fired" means.
Good. So this isn't
a bad idea anymore.
Can I be fired, too?
♪ Men. ♪
♪Men. ♪
Okay. (grunts)
Okay.
Um, I just, uh, want
to point out that,
uh, due
to my engorged testicles,
uh, my penis is not currently
to scale,
so...
Yeah, yeah, here it is.
When you pulled out the tick,
you didn't get all of it
so it got inflamed.
Oh.
(groans)
It's like you're the Hulk,
but only your balls got angry.
You know, this is what
relationships are all about.
Watching your girlfriend pull
a tick out of your uncle's junk.
Aw. I'm your girlfriend?
If it's a boy, name it Walden.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man